<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application1.33</string>

    <string name="article_title">Cats</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Amazing facts about cats</string>
    <string name="article">Outdoor intact (Tom Cats) males cover 3 to 5 miles of their trails of previously marked territory.  Daily rounds assure the cat that his turf is well scented
10 million more cats are kept as pets than dogs
Every cat carries the Tabby gene
Most adult cats lack the enzymes necessary to digest milk
Most of a kitten’s growth takes place during sleep
As a kitten matures, its 26 milk teeth are replaced by 30 permanent teeth
The kitten’s permanent teeth grow in between the ages of 12 to 18 weeks
The hunting instinct is buried deeply in the mind of even the youngest kittens.  Rather than just eat its food, a kitten visually examines it and will paw at it, as it would an animal brought back from the hunt, to check if it is safe to approach
Cats are most active in the morning and evening (dawn and twilight)—the prime hunting hours
After a successful hunt for mice or a toy, many cats engage in a tension releasing dance. It builds the cats self-esteem and confidence
Cats prefer foods at body temperature—the temperature of freshly killed prey
While hunting the whiskers can reach forward to give information about the prey they stalk
The cat’s whiskers have developed into antennae and help detect movement nearby
A cat’s sensitive whiskers can detect even slight changes in air pressure and air currents—giving the cat “radar” at night, or insight of a storm about to come
Cats are either right- or left-pawed (handed), showing a distinct preference for one paw over the other
When cats purr, it is an expression of intense emotion, meaning pleasure or pain
The domestic cat is the only feline that can hold its tail in a vertical position while walking, wild cats must hold the tail horizontally or tucked between their legs
Cats, Camels and Giraffes walk with 2 right and 2 left legs</string>
</resources>
